<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thought before Tools</title><link>https://bongosway.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Thought before Tools</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 07:57:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bongosway.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Beginner's Guide to Designing Page Objects - Pt.1</title><link>https://bongosway.github.io/posts/a-beginners-guide-to-designing-page-objects-pt.1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 07:57:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://bongosway.github.io/posts/a-beginners-guide-to-designing-page-objects-pt.1/</guid><description>Introduction Page Object is a popular design pattern used to represent services provided by a page (reads the rendered page you see on your screen) especially when writing test against a web page. This pattern is mainly popularised by the Selenium Browser Automation tool.
In this guide, we create a Page Object for the the Google home and search results page.
When you&amp;rsquo;re finished, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to create effective page objects for any UI interface you encounter.</description></item><item><title>Should I Remove PageObjects from my Test Class?</title><link>https://bongosway.github.io/posts/should-i-remove-pageobjects-from-my-test-class/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 10:32:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://bongosway.github.io/posts/should-i-remove-pageobjects-from-my-test-class/</guid><description>The short answer is YES!
Introduction The Page Object Pattern is a popular design pattern used to represent services provided by a page (reads the rendered page you see on your screen). Whilst this is a good pattern to drive the application under test, it should not be visible to the test class.
Why? The test class is no longer isolated from internal code changes Binds the test class to the underlying technology/library Low-level code details pollute the test class The test class should represent the domain behaviours only, not the implementation.</description></item><item><title>How to solve the NoSuchMethodError toImmutableSet() error when using Google Autoservice</title><link>https://bongosway.github.io/posts/how-to-solve-the-nosuchmethoderror-toimmutableset-error-when-using-google-autoservice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bongosway.github.io/posts/how-to-solve-the-nosuchmethoderror-toimmutableset-error-when-using-google-autoservice/</guid><description>Introduction Whilst building a demo application showcasing google AutoService, I encountered the below error:
java.lang.NoSuchMethodError: com.google.common.collect.ImmutableSet.toImmutableSet()Ljava/util/stream/Collector; Searching through the internet, most solutions recommended upgrading the Google Guava version but that did not resolve the problem.
The main cause of this error, was putting the wrong Autoservice dependency in the classpath.
If your POM file has the below dependency, then you are most likely get this error.
&amp;lt;/dependencies&amp;gt; &amp;lt;dependency&amp;gt; &amp;lt;groupId&amp;gt;com.google.auto.service&amp;lt;/groupId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;artifactId&amp;gt;auto-service&amp;lt;/artifactId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;1.</description></item></channel></rss>